winentrance.com 2010-12-25

# Winentrance.com - Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment To Privacy :**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

At [www.winentrance.com](http://www.winentrance.com/ "www.winentrance.com"), we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit [www.winentrance.com](http://www.winentrance.com/ "www.winentrance.com"), and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on [www.winentrance.com](http://www.winentrance.com/ "www.winentrance.com") to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New Delhi real estate ads to someone in Delhi, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing Educational ads to someone who frequents education sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

In addition, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads to our site. Google's use of the Dart cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Visitors may opt out of the Dart cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Google may use interest based advertising where they recognize the types of web pages users visit across the Adsense network. This helps advertisers reach users on the basis of their interests.

**The Way We Use Information :**

WinEntrance.com may use this information for internal marketing and promotional purposes. We may use this information to get in touch with you when necessary and inform you of new services and features. 

WinEntrance.com may like to update viewers with information on related issues, which the users may find interesting. 

We do not share this information with outside parties, but we may share your information with advertisers on an aggregate basis only.

#### Winentrance.com - Privacy Policy
